Shane Fields

Software Developer

Auburndale, Fl

863-450-5601 | shanedfields97@gmail.com

LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY

I am a proactive, bold, and growth-oriented developer with a strong drive and willingness to learn new things. I love creating simple and effective UI that optimizes user's experience. My personal mission is to further my specialization in frontend development, solve difficult problems, work with amazing people and develop cool technologies.

SKILLS

Programming Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Node.is.

Related Professional Skills: Bootstrap, Algorithms & Data Structures, GitHub, Postman, Word, Excel, and digital marketing.

PROJECTS

Pomodoro Timer / Project Link

- Aids in productivity.
- Ability to set and control timer settings and session time.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Business Website / Project Link

- Professional website for a local business.
- Built out product pages for companies catalog.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, BootStrap

Newsletter Signup | Project Link

- Modern signup page for a newsletter
- Retrieves information user inputs via API and shows success/error message once complete.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, BootStrap 5, JavaScript, Mailchimp API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

Jan 2022 - Present

Shane Codes

- Design creative websites with precise functionality.
- Work with clients to build modern and professional websites that best suits their needs.
- Support website stability and online branding.

Warehouse Manager - Sales

Florida Wire Fabricators | Winter Haven, Fl

Nov 2016 - Present

- Manage the manufacturing of wire products used by agricultural businesses around the country.
- Sales representative that contacts prospective clients and continues to build relationships with current clients.

Package Handler

UPS | Lakeland, Fl

June 2020 - Present

- Assists in the unloading and loading of delivery trucks and the distribution of packages to other departments in the warehouse.
- Communicates with drivers and supervisors to optimize the organization of packages for each individual route.

EDUCATION

Engineering Flex Program

March 2021 - November 2021

Thinkful

- Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards.
- Focused on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Node.js, and algorithms & data structures.
- Built comprehensive projects and collaborated with students and mentors to resolve issues and expand my skill set.